<dcmi-types>	<dcmi-type label="Collection" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Collection">		A collection is an aggregation of items. The term		collection means that the resource is described as a		group; its parts may be separately described and navigated. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Dataset" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Dataset">		A dataset is information encoded in a defined structure 		(for example, lists, tables, and databases), intended to		be useful for direct machine processing. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Event" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Event">		An event is a non-persistent, time-based occurrence.		Metadata for an event provides descriptive		information that is the basis for discovery of the		purpose, location, duration, responsible agents, and		links to related events and resources.  The resource		of type event may not be retrievable if the described		instantiation has expired or is yet to occur.		Examples - exhibition, web-cast, conference,		workshop, open-day, performance, battle, trial,		wedding, tea-party, conflagration. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Image" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Image">		An image is a primarily symbolic visual representation		other than text. For example - images and photographs of		physical objects, paintings, prints, drawings, other		images and graphics, animations and moving pictures,		film, diagrams, maps, musical notation. Note that image		may include both electronic and physical representations. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Interactive Resource" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/InteractiveResource">		An interactive resource is a resource which requires		interaction from the user to be understood, executed,		or experienced. For example - forms on web pages, applets,		multimedia learning objects, chat services, virtual		reality. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Service" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Service">		A service is a system that provides one or more		functions of value to the end-user. Examples include:		a photocopying service, a banking service, an		authentication service, interlibrary loans, a Z39.50		or Web server. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Software" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Software">		Software is a computer program in source or		compiled form which may be available for installation		non-transiently on another machine. For software which		exists only to create an interactive environment, use		interactive instead. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Sound" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Sound">		A sound is a resource whose content is primarily		intended to be rendered as audio. For example - a		music playback file format, an audio compact disc,		and recorded speech or sounds. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Text" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/Text">		A text is a resource whose content is primarily		words for reading. For example - books, letters,		dissertations, poems, newspapers, articles,		archives of mailing lists. Note that facsimiles		or images of texts are still of the genre text. 	</dcmi-type>	<dcmi-type label="Physical Object" identifier="http://purl.org/dc/dcmitype/PhysicalObject">		An inanimate, three-dimensional object or substance.		For example -- a computer, the great pyramid, a		sculpture.  Note that digital representations		of, or surrogates for, these things should use Image,		Text or one of the other types. 	</dcmi-type></dcmi-types>